

122a, jalan pju 10/14d, saujana damansara, 47810 petaling jaya, selangor. 012 657 6667 akieyap@gmail.com

# Professional Summary

I have design and visual merchandise experience and was working on detailed projects. I also possess over 5 years of experience on several team-designed projects ranging from logo design to creating promotional materials for a business and have experience for conceptualize and implement visual merchandising strategies in the store, event or promotional area. I am very dedicated to my work.

# Work Experience

### Senior Graphic Designer Cum MARCOM

Berjaya Air S/B July 2013 - Present

- Development and production of any marketing materials such as promotional materials, outdoor advertisements, exhibition & events, website content.
- Prepare and assemble final layouts for printing.
- Assist to manage all social media such as Facebook and Twitter for the Company.
- Review and edit existing promotional materials for marketing effectiveness, cross selling implications and make sure it adheres to the brand's guidelines
- Work closely with a team to create and manage cross-organizational and integrated marketing strategies.
- · Serve as the Company's liaison of all advertisements bookings.
- To coordinate media schedule in a monthly basis for printing and online advertisement.

# Senior Graphic Designer Cum Visual Merchandiser

ADVANCED APOTHĒKE S/B

June 2012- June 2013

- Responsible Four Beauty Brand carried by the Company -L'erbolario from Italy, Neal's Yard Remedies from London, Penhaligon's from London-Perfume, Les Fleus de Bach
- Responsibilities in organising and attending press tours and events, which include arranging and organising a high frequency of media related events such as press luncheons and sampling of new product.
- Planning and execution on all Marketing programs including road show, exhibition, product launching, customers loyalty program, social media's activities
- Assist the company in the overall marketing plans and strategies. Conceptualize and implement visual merchandising strategies in the store, event or
- · Assist in multimedia projects and other marketing related tasks when required for example sending new product to media, listing new product features to publisher, send
- Responsible for creating and setting up all visual merchandising and promotional display for seasonal change and promotional event.
- Decide what goes into the display window, and how often to come up with new window display ideas Plan the layout of various items that are stacked inside the store, in a manner that encour-
- ages greater customer interest and sales.
- Come up with promotional ideas and marketing gimmicks in order to attract more buyers and generate more attention.
- Liaise closely with suppliers on print material & ensure the outputs arrive on time
- Manage the purchase budget, production costing and pricing
- · Conceptualize and design marketing communications & supported materials, such as brochures, banners, posters, packaging, EDM, advertisements, presentations for relevant promotions

# Senior Graphic Designer

- Responsible for branding the top adoption related campaign with associated logos, collateral, trade show displays, print ads, packaging designs, and promotional pieces.
- Responsible for meeting clients and fulfilled their needs and requirements.
- Responsible for delivering projects from concept through to production.
- To provide appealing design solutions that reflect current trends, brand standards and a strategic approach to problem solving.
- Works with Design lead on specific aspects of each design projects. Maintains projects schedules, timelines and budgets and assists in preparation for team and project meetings.
- Know how to communicate visually and verbally to solve problem and organize work flow
- Experience in printing and production, to spec materials for cost and troubleshoot artwork/ printing problems
- Responsible for maintaining and up keeping the company brand identity as well as brainstorm new ideas for the existing and new clients required by the design brief

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma in Graphic Design 2004 - 2007 Dasein Academy of Art

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mandarin: Execellent spoken & written B.Melayu: Fair spoken & written

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Shoes Design Competition 2006 3rd runner up

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

### REFERENCE

Ricky Chan

Senior Business Development Manager Berjaya Air S/B

# Derek Yeap

Business Development Director Advanced Apotheke Sdn Bhd

# Michelle Yap

Creative Director Carnaby Studio